obesityQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "Which fat is more dangerous subcutaneous or visceral? ",
        "answer": "visceral",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The high risk waist circumference for men is ____ inches or ____ cm",
        "answer": "40, 102",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The high risk waist circumference for women is ____ inches or ____ cm",
        "answer": "35, 88",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Metabolic syndrome involves waist circumference greater than ____ inches in men or ____inches in women",
        "answer": "40, 35",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Metabolic syndrome involves serum triglycerides of ____mg/dL or greater",
        "answer": "150",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Metabolic syndrome involves high density lipoprotein cholesterol less than ____ mg/dL in men or less than ____ mg/dL in women",
        "answer": "40, 50",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Metabolic syndrome involves blood pressure level of ____ mmHg or higher",
        "answer": "130/85",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Metabolic syndrome involves serum glucose of ____ mg/dL or greater",
        "answer": "100",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Obesity etiologies include g____, m____, e____, m____ ____",
        "answer": "genetic, metabolic, environmental, medication induced",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Environmental obesity etiologies include: ____ and lifestyle, ____ inactivity",
        "answer": "diet, physical",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Medication induced obesity etiologies include: ____, DM medications such as ____, ____, ____, highly active ____ therapy, ____ hormones",
        "answer": "psychotropics, insulin, sulfonylurea, thiazolidinediones, antiretroviral, steroid",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the consequences of obesity: ____disease, hypertension, ____, DM, ____stroke, cancer, ____apnea, osteoarthritis",
        "answer": "cardiovascular, dyslipidemia, sleep",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the correct self exclusions: a. Severe obesity (BMI>40, b. pregnancy or breast feeding, c. <18 years of age or >65 years of age, d. cardiovascular disease, dyslipidemia, DM, or HTN, e. eating disorders",
        "choices": "a and b, c and d, none of the above, all of the above",
		"answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Weight needs to be lost when BMI > ____, or BMI > ____ with ____ risk factors, high risk waist circumference with > ____ risk factors, men > ____ inches, women > ____ inches",
        "answer": "30, 27, 2, 2, 40, 35",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "____ modification is the most commonly used and most important for weight loss",
        "answer": "dietary",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "AHA/ACC/TOS recommends reduce food calorie intake ____ - ____ kcal/d for women and ____ - ____kcal/d for men",
        "answer": "1200, 1500, 1500, 1800",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "AHA/ACC/TOS recommends losing ____ to ____ pounds/week based on a calorie deficit of ____ to ____ kcal/day",
        "answer": "1, 2, 500, 750",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The initial goal of dietary modification is to reduce body weight by ____ to ____ from baselie over ____ months",
        "answer": "5, 10, 6",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Physical activity is especially important for weight loss ____",
        "answer": "maintenance",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adults are recommended ____ minutes of moderate aerobic activity or ____ minutes of vigorous physical activity per week equalling ____ minutes ____ times/week",
        "answer": "150, 75, 30, 5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "To meet weight control goals ____ minutes of moderate intensity aerobic activity is recommended",
        "answer": "300",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Children/adolescents are recommended > ____ minutes of moderate or vigorous aerobic activity a day, including vigorous activity at least ____ days/week",
        "answer": "60, 3",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "____ therapy is most important for weight loss",
        "answer": "dietary",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are practical behavior tips for patients for weight loss, focus on ____ change at a time, ____ control is key, ____ method",
        "answer": "one, portion, plate",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the plate method, fill ____ the plate with ____ ",
        "answer": "half, vegetables",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the plate method, fill a ____ of the plate with ____ foods",
        "answer": "quarter, starchy",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the plate method, fill a ____ of the plate with ____",
        "answer": "quarter, meat",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the patient does not lose ____ kg in the first ____ weeks of initiating medication, there is a ____ likelihood of response",
        "answer": "2, 4, low",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat is indicated for patients with BMI ____ or higher",
        "answer": "25",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat is approved for ages ____ and older for long term use of ____ months",
        "answer": "18, 12",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat MOA is that it inhibits absorption of dietary fats by inhibiting the ____ of ____",
        "answer": "hydrolysis of triglycerides",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat is metbolized in ____ wall, ____ to ____ is excreted via ____",
        "answer": "intestinal, 95, 97, feces",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat OTC dose is ____mg ____ times a day",
        "answer": "60, 3",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat is pregnancy category ____",
        "answer": "X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most patients in clinical trials lost ____ to ____ pounds over ____ months",
        "answer": "5, 10, 6",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adverse effects of Orlistat include: ____, loose ____, ____ stools, ____urgency, fecal ____",
        "answer": "flatulence, stools, fatty, fecal, incontinence",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat decreases absorption of ____ soluble vitamins ____, ____, ____, ____",
        "answer": "fat, D, A, K, E",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat should be avoided in patients taking ____, ____, and ____",
        "answer": "cyclosporine, levothyroxine, amiodarone",
        "type": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orlistat may increase effects of ____",
        "answer": "warfarin",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prescription medications are reserved for patients with BMI > ____ or higher, BMI > ____ or higher with concomitant disease or risk factors",
        "answer": "30, 27",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine is approved for short term use of ____ to ____ weeks, max ____ months",
        "answer": "8, 12, 6",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine is cautioned in patients with mod-sev ____, ____ impairment",
        "answer": "HTN, renal",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine is pregnancy category ____",
        "answer": "X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adverse effects of Phentermine include : c____, h____, in____, t____, t____, i____ BP",
        "answer": "constipation, headache, insomnia, tremor, tachycardia, increased BP",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine tolerance develops within a ____ weeks",
        "answer": "few",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine/Topiramate ER is discontinued or escalated if ____% weight loss is not acheived after ____ weeks on 7.6/46mg",
        "answer": "3, 12",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phentermine/Topiramate Er is discontinued if ____% weight loss is not achieved after ____ weeks on max daily dose",
        "answer": "5, 12",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adverse effects of Phentermine/Topiramate ER include d____, c____, p____, a____, d____",
        "answer": "dizziness, constipation, paresthesia, altered taste, dry mouth",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the REMS for Phentermine/Topiramate ER",
        "answer": "fetal defects",
        "type": "text"
     },
    {
        "question": "Lorcaserin is pregnancy category ____",
        "answer": "X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lorcaserin is dosed at ____ mg ____ times a day",
        "answer": "10, 2",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Locaserin is discontinued at week ____ if ____% weight loss has not been achieved",
        "answer": "12, 5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Locaserin adverse effects include: d____, d____, d____, s____, c____, f____",
        "answer": "dizziness, dry mouth, depression, suicidal ideation, constipation, fatigue",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Locaserin may increase levels of drugs metabolized by ____",
        "answer": "CYP2D6",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naltrexone/Buproprion SR is FDA approved for ____ term use",
        "answer": "long",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naltrexone/Buproprion should not be taken with high____ meals",
        "answer": "fat",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naltrexone/Bupropion should be discontinued if patient has not lost ____% BW in ____ weeks",
        "answer": "5, 12",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adverse effects of Naltrexone/Bupropion are N____, i____, H____, c____, d____, d____",
        "answer": "N/V/D, insomnia, constipation, dry mouth, dizziness",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naltrexone/Bupropion is pregnancy category ____",
        "answer": "X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naltrexone/Bupropion has a ____ box warning that it increases ____ ideation, and behavior",
        "answer": "black, suicidal",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liraglutide is FDA approved for ____ management",
        "answer": "weight",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liraglutide has a ____ box warning that it induces ____ C cell tumors in rats",
        "answer": "black, thyroid",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liraglutide should be avoided with other ____ agonist",
        "answer": "GLP-1",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liraglutide is pregnancy category ____",
        "answer": "C",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liraglutide requires ____ because of black box warning",
        "answer": "REMS",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bitter orange contains ____ which is similar to epinephrine",
        "answer": "synephrine",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Other names for Ephedra include Ma ____ and ____ tea",
        "answer": "Huang, Mormon",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Caffeine Green Tea Extract also acts as a ____",
        "answer": "diuretic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Caffeine green tea extract has interactions with blood ____ lowering agents and ____",
        "answer": "glucose, alendronate",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chromium is an ____ trace element",
        "answer": "essential",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chromium plays a role in ____ regulation in body and cofactor for enzymes involved in energy production",
        "answer": "insulin",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chromium is naturally present in on____, t____, oy____, p____",
        "answer": "onion, tomatoes, oysters, potatoes",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Risks associated with chromium include r____, r____ failure, m____,  s____, and b____ sugar changes",
        "answer": "rhabdomyolysis, renal, mood, sleep, blood",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Raspberry ketone is similar to ____ and ____",
        "answer": "synephrine, capsaicin",
        "type": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "Raspberry ketone causes ____ and increases ____ production",
        "answer": "lipolysis, adiponectin",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Raspberry ketone has interactions with ____ and ____",
        "answer": "warfarin, hypoglycemia",
        "type": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoodia is an ____ supressant",
        "answer": "appetite",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Garcinia cambogia is rich in ____ acid and is promoted to supress ____ and inhibit ____ production",
        "answer": "hydroxycitric, supress, fat",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Risks of Garcinia cambogia is increased s____, r____, h____, d____",
        "answer": "serotonin, rhabdomyolysis, hypoglycemia, dementia",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Psyllium and Guar Gum is used for ____ and ____ as a bulk laxative",
        "answer": "hypercholesterolemia, constipation",
        "type": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chitosan is a structural component of c____, i____ and s____",
        "answer": "crustaceans, insects, spiders",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chitosan is marketed as ____ absorption blocker",
        "answer": "fat",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cortisol blockers has the common ingredients ____ and ____",
        "answer": "phosphatidylserine, L-theanine",
        "type": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "Laxatives should not be used long term for over ____ weeks",
        "answer": "2",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
       "question": "Obesity Class I is BMI ____ to ____",
        "answer": "30, 34.9",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Obesity Class II is BMI ____ to ____",
        "answer": "35, 39.9",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Obesity Class III is BMI >=",
        "answer": "40",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "BMI 30-34.9 is Obesity ____",
        "answer": "I",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "BMI 35-39.9 is Obesity Class ____",
        "answer": "II",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "BMI >=40 is Obesity Class ____",
        "answer": "III",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Underweight is classified as BMI <____",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Normal BMI is between BMI ____ - ____",
        "answer": "18.5-24.9",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Overweight BMI is ____ - ____",
        "answer": "25-29.9",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of phentermine is",
        "answer": "Adipex-P",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Phntermine/Topiramate ER is",
        "answer": "Qsymia",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name for Locaserin is",
        "answer": "Belviq",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Naltrexone/Bupropion SR is",
        "answer": "Contrave",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Liraglutide is",
        "answer": "Saxenda",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Adipex-P is",
        "answer": "Phentermine",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of phentermine is",
        "answer": "Adipex-P",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Diethylpropion is",
        "answer": "Tenuate",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name is Benzphetamine is",
        "answer": "Didrex",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Qsymia is",
        "answer": "phentermine/topiramate ER",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Belviq is",
        "answer": "Lorcaserin",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Contrave is",
        "answer": "naltrexone/bupropion SR",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of phentermine is",
        "answer": "Adipex-P",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Phntermine/Topiramate ER is",
        "answer": "Qsymia",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name for Locaserin is",
        "answer": "Belviq",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Naltrexone/Bupropion SR is",
        "answer": "Contrave",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Saxenda is",
        "answer": "Liraglutide",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Tenuate is",
        "answer": "Diethylpropioin",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Didrex is",
        "answer": "Benzphetamine",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of phentermine is stimulating the hypothalamus to release ____ to suppres appetite",
        "answer": "NE",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of diethylpropion is to stimulate ____ release to supress ____ signals and appetite",
        "answer": "catecholamine, hunger",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of benzphetamine is to stimulate ____ release to supress ____ signals and appetite",
        "answer": "catecholamine, hunger",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA for orilistat is that it inhibits ____ absorption by forming bond with ____ and ____ lipase",
        "answer": "nutrient, gastric, pancreatic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA for lorcaserin is it is a selective ____ agonist which supresses appetite",
        "answer": "5HT2C",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of phentermine and topiramate is phentermine stimulates ____ release to supress appetite and topiramate suppresses appetite and enhances ____",
        "answer": "NE, satiety",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of topiramate is it increases ____ and reduces cravings for food by decreasing GI motility, increasing ____ aversion and increasing energy expenditure",
        "answer": "satiety, taste",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of liraglutide is it is a ____ receptor agonist and a physiological regulator of appetite and calorie intake and also stimulates ____ and decreases ____",
        "answer": "GLP-1, insulin, glucagon",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The MOA of naltrexone/bupropion SR is it is an opioid ____ and dopamine/NE reuptake inhibitor which suppresses appetite",
        "answer": "antagonist",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The trade name of Orilistat is",
        "answer": "Xenical",
        "type": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "The generic name of Xenical is",
        "answer": "Orilistat",
        "type": "text"
	}
]
